cari.com.my 2003-06-10

# Malaysia? = CARI!!

**CARI's Online Privacy Policy**

Your right to privacy is very important. Werecognise that when you choose to provide us with informationabout yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. 

We believe this information should only be usedto help us provide you with better service. That's why we haveput a policy in place to protect your personal information. 

Below is a summary of our policy. 

What personal information do we collect?  
In general, when you visit our websites andaccess information you remain anonymous. Before we ask you forinformation, we will explain how this information will be used.We will not provide any of your personal information to othercompanies or individuals without your permission. 

Some of our sites require registration toaccess, although typically all that's requested is an e-mailaddress and some basic information about you. 

There are occasions where we will ask foradditional information. We do this to be able to betterunderstand your needs, and provide you with services that webelieve may be valuable to you. Some examples of information ourwebsites collect are name, email, home page address, and personalinfo. We give you the opportunity to elect not to receivematerials from us. 

If you sign up for CARI's electronic newsletteror e-mail list, each message will include instructions on how to"unsubscribe" from that list. 

Protecting your privacy  
We will take appropriate steps to protectyour privacy. Whenever you provide sensitive information (forexample, a credit card number to make a purchase), we will takereasonable steps to protect it, such as encrypting your cardnumber. We will also take reasonable security measures to protectyour personal information in storage. Credit card numbers areused only for payment processing and are not retained formarketing purposes. 

We will not provide any of your personalinformation to other companies or individuals without yourpermission. 

Our websites provide links to other web sites.  
Since we do not control those websites, we encourage you toreview the privacy policies of these web sites. 

Use of cookies  
CARI websites may use cookies for variousreasons. Cookies enable us to provide you with a betterexperience by allowing us to understand what areas of the websiteare of interest to our visitors. These cookies do not trackindividual information. 

CARI also uses cookies when you register forone of our web programs. In this situation, a cookie will storeuseful information that enables our website to remember you whenyou return to visit us. 

Cookies from CARI websites can only be read byCARI websites. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser,you can still access most of our websites. This site, www.cari.com.my, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data, typically through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to [http://www.engage.com/privacy .](http://www.engage.com/privacy)

CARI content providers, advertisers andpartners 

CARI will not provide your personal informationto anyone outside of CARI and its parent companies except in thelimited circumstances mentioned, and only then with your consent.For instance, the personal information you provide duringregistration to the CARI Finance centre "powered by"Malaysia will not be shared with anyone outside of Malaysia. 

However, CARI cannot control the practices ofother partners and advertisers. If you have provided personalinformation to a party or advertiser connected with CARI and havenot been informed by CARI as to its purpose, contact themdirectly by going to their home page and looking for a companyprofile or information area. 

It is important to note that CARI contains manylinks to sites other than CARI, and that those sites may notfollow the same privacy policies as CARI. For instance, if youclick an ad or a search result on CARI, this will take you awayfrom CARI and to an entirely different site. This includes linksfrom advertisers, content providers and partners who may useCARI's logo and/or style as part of a co-branding agreement.These sites may send their own cookies to you, and as a result,may collect data and ask for personal information that CARI wouldnot. 

Kids and privacy 

CARI requests that children under 18 do notsubmit or post any information to the site without a parent's orguardian's consent. However, we will not request or knowinglycollect from a child any information online that can be traced tothe child, such as an e-mail address, name, or information aboutthe child's family. 

Unless a parent or guardian consents to suchuse in advance, CARI will not knowingly use information that achild provides to CARI for any marketing, selling or promotionalpurposes. 

Changes to policy 

CARI reserves the right to change this policyat any time by notifying guests of the existence of a revisedprivacy policy.
